- 好了选张卡   - 好
- Pick a card.     - Okay.
现在记住花色号码
All right. Now memorize it.
- 好了没？ - 好了
- You got it?     - Oh, yes.
好 是这张吗？
Okay. Is that your card?
- 就是这张   - 哈哈
- Yes.     - Ha, ha.
- 大家好   - 嗨
- Hey, guys.     - Hi there.
你们猜怎么着？班要上电视拍广告了
Guess what. Ben is gonna be in a TV commercial.
- 你们在说什么？ - 还没有定案
- What are you talking about?     - Well, it's not for sure.
不过我们在公园里遇到一个人 他觉得班很可爱
But, uh, we met this guy in the park who thought Ben was really cute.
这也是事实啦 所以那个人留了张名片…
You know, which he is. Um, anyhoo, he gave us his card...
要我带班去参加广告试镜
...and told us to bring him down for this commercial he's auditioning.
哇哦
Whoa.
这个人是本地最大的选角导演
The guy's like the biggest commercial casting director in town.
班去公园随便散个步 就有试镜自动送上门
Ben takes one lousy walk in the park and gets an audition?
我是说 班 真有你的
I mean, way to go, Ben!
那个公园我都去烂了 从来没人主动找我去试镜
Man, I've been in that park a million times. No one's ever offered me an audition.
我知道 真的很神奇 我们只是在陪班玩荡秋千…
I know, it's crazy. We were just pushing Ben on the swings...
我每次都玩荡秋千啊
I'm always on the swings.
我是哪里做错了？
What am I doing wrong?
就是荡秋千那里
That.
- 好 我要出门了 祝我好运   - 祝你好运
- Okay, gotta go. Wish me luck.     - Good luck.
瑞秋 既然你在罗夫罗兰工作 能不能带几件马球衫回来？
Hey, Rach, now that you working at Ralph Lauren, can you get me some shirts?
第一天上班就偷公司东西 我可能…
Uh, well, you know what? I don't know if I'd feel comfortable stealing...
下不了手喔
...on my very first day.
不愿意慷公司之慨
Unwilling to steal from work.
有意思了
Interesting.
就算有人能拿免费的 那也非我莫属
Besides, if anybody is gonna get free stuff, it's me.
好了 各位 祝我好运吧
Okay, guys, way to wish me luck.
- 给他们好看   - 拜
- Go get them.     - Bye.
好 来讨论帮瑞秋庆生的事
Okay, let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
我建议在这周末办惊喜派对
I say we throw a surprise party this weekend.
哇哦 可是一个月后才是她生日啊
Whoa, whoa. But her birthday's not for another month.
是没错 但在生日当天开派对 那就不惊喜啦
Okay, but if we throw her a party on her birthday, then it's not a surprise.
我觉得这主意不错 我们办个晚养派对邀请好朋友过来
I think that's a great idea. We can have a dinner party and invite her close friends.
罗斯 我们要帮瑞秋办惊喜派对罗
Ross. We're having a surprise party for Rachel.
- 好   - 搞定
- Okay.     - Done.
好 那你要一起办吗？
Okay, great. So do you wanna do it together?
乐意之至
I would love to do it together.
她们要一起来耶
They're gonna do it together.
兄弟 那位可是我女友
Dude, that's my girlfriend.
所以我就得闭嘴？
So I gotta shut it down now?
好 我得走了
All right, I gotta take off. I'm picking up Ben...
我要接班去参加大试镜
...and then we're off to the big audition.
看到有演员假装是班的父亲 那种感觉一定很怪
It's gonna be weird seeing some actor pretending to be Ben's dad.
- 是啊   - 怪过看班的两个妈妈温存？
- Yeah.     - Weirder than his two moms making out?
爸爸？广告里面有爸爸？
Whoa, whoa. Dad? There's a dad in the commercial?
是啊 班和爸爸喝汤 演得很陶醉的样子
Yeah. The dad and Ben eat soup and pretend to enjoy it.
或许我可以跟你们一起去 搞不好能试镜演那个爸爸
Well, maybe I'll go with you and see if I can audition as the dad.
说到扮演班的爸爸 由我这教父上场最适合了
I mean, who better to play Ben's father than his godfather?
- 你不是班的教父   - 什么？
- You're not his godfather.     - What?
你在开玩笑吧？
Are you kidding?
当然是啊
Of course I am.
- 我们走吧 教父   - 好 哈哈
- Okay, let's go, godfather.     - All right. Ha, ha.
我获选了 他们让我试镜
Hey, I'm in. They're gonna let me audition.
真的？太棒了
Really? That's great.
我知道 有个女的看过我演舞台剧
I know, I know. One of the casting ladies has actually seen me in a play.
所以我离她离得远远的
So I steered clear of her.
- 那个孩子看起来很眼熟   - 哦 耶
- That kid looks familiar.     - Oh, yeah.
是啊 他拍过一堆广告
Yeah, he's done tons of commercials.
有糖果广告 新力游戏机
I've seen him in Sugar Smacks, PlayStation...
还帮电话公司拍过广告
...and that one for the phone company.
他演得实在是太好了…
In fact, he was so good in that one...
我索性跟着换了电话公司
...he actually convinced me to switch phone companies.
钱德因此还气得半死
Chandler was mad.
不过他这次休想拿到这角色 因为班比他可爱多了
Yeah, well, he's not gonna get this one. All right? Ben is way cuter than that kid.
看就知道 宝贝 看看你
I mean, look at him.
很好
That's great.
不过若我能演班的爸爸 这样是不是很棒？
Listen, wouldn't it be great if I got to play Ben's dad?
乔伊 你跟班一点都不像
Joey, you look nothing like Ben.
比你跟他像多了
I look more like him than you do.
我跟你还不熟 哪里生得出小孩？
Well, I really don't know you well enough for you to do that.
现在是最后的二选一 南西 我知道你喜欢这一个…
So it's down to these two. Nancy, I know you like this one...
我也有同感 瑞秋 你觉得呢？
...and I think I agree. Rachel, what do you think?
那个是很漂亮
Well, um, that one is pretty...
但我超爱这个质料 抱歉了
...but I just love this fabric. Sorry.
不用抱歉 提供意见是你的职责之一
Oh, don't be. That's part of your job here, to give your opinions.
功劳归我 开玩笑的
And then I take credit for them. I'm kidding. Ha, ha.
她这次是在开玩笑 但下次可别跟她意见相左
She is kidding. But don't ever disagree with her again.
- 这次换我在开玩笑   - 哦 哈哈
- Okay, now I'm kidding.     - Oh, ha, ha.
这个办公室真有趣
Oh, what a fun office.
我不知道要选哪一个 不过先来根烟倒是真的
I don't know which one. But I do know I need a cigarette.
不如我们出去休息一下
So, what do you say we take a break, go outside...
等回来之后再解决？
...and figure this out when we come back.
- 瑞秋？ - 嗯
- Rachel?     - Yeah.
- 你抽烟吗？ - 不抽
- You smoke?     - No.
我爸是医生 老跟我说些恐怖的故事…
My dad's a doctor. And he would always tell me just horror stories...
说那些鬼神精灵的…
About ghosts and goblins...
完全赞同公主抽烟的权利
...who totally supported the princess' right to smoke.
她们在抽烟的时候…
And then they came back from smoking...
就背着我做出了决定
...and they'd made all of the decisions without me.
- 这样不太公平   - 我知道啊
- That doesn't seem fair.     - I know.
我不同流合污还被处罚 抽烟可是恶心又伤身的习惯
It's like I'm being punished for not having this disgusting, poisonous habit.
对 抽烟最棒了
Yeah, it is the best.
万一这种事没完没了怎么办？
I mean, what if this keeps happening?
她们在外头抽烟做决定
They'll be outside smoking, making all the decisions...
我只能在办公室里 呼吸愚蠢的新鲜空气
...and I'll just be up in my office breathing in my stupid clean air.
到时等阿金要升我们的职…
You know? And when Kim wants to promote one of us...
你们想她会选谁？是我还是乌烟瘴气的冒烟女？
...who do you think she's gonna pick? Me or Smokey Smokerson?
瑞秋 你也可以一起去 不用抽烟
Rachel, you can go down there, you don't have to smoke.
就说要去透透气
Just say you wanna get some fresh air.
对 这我做得到
Yeah, I could do that.
简单点的就是一起抽烟
Yeah, or you could just do the easy thing and smoke.
- 嘿 瑞秋 要去喝咖啡吗？ - 嘿
- Hey. Do you wanna go get coffee?     - Hey.
- 乐意之至   - 好
- Oh, I would love to.     - Oh, good.
- 宝贝 我也想起去   - 好啊
- I'm gonna go too, babe.     - Oh, good.
- 哇   - 哇
- Yay.     - Yay.
等等 我变卦了
Oh, I changed my mind.
好 来讨论派对的事 我有一大堆点子
Okay, let's talk about the party. I have so many ideas.
- 我也是   - 哦
- Ooh, me too.     - Oh!
- 耶   - 真是壮观
- Yeah!     - Oh, look at that.
- 好 这是蛋糕的素描图   - 哇哦
- All right. This is a little sketch of the cake.     - Uh-huh. Wow.
还有一些菜单的样本
See? Um, some sample menus.
不如用异国小点心当前菜
Um, you know, I thought we'd start with a Tuscan-style finger food.
至于音乐呢 这是我CD收藏的字母列表
Okay. And for music, here's an alphabetized list of all of my CDs.
跟食物超搭配的还做了记号
I've highlighted the ones that'll go really good with the food.
- 不是说要亲密的晚餐派对吗？ - 现在不那样做了
- What happened to the dinner party?     - We're not doing that.
- 好？那么…   - 哇哦 好…
- Okay? So...     - Wow. All right.
看来你全包办了 多谢 "共同"主办人
Looks like you took care of everything. Thanks a lot, cohost.
怎么了？我没有一手包办啊
Wait. I didn't take care of everything.
你要做的事还有很多
There's plenty of things for you to do.
举个例子
Uh-huh? Like what?
杯子
Cups.
杯子？你让我准备杯子？
Cups. You're giving me cups?
还有冰块
And ice.
杯子和冰块？我可以负责杯子和冰块？
Cups and ice? Oh, I get to be in charge of cups and ice?
好吧…
All right.
行 我就负责杯子和冰块
Fine. Okay, I will be in charge of cups and ice.
- 等等 冰块可以从餐厅拿…   - 冰块是我的
- Wait, I can get ice at the restaurant...     - I got it.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
- 试镜顺利吗？ - 不太顺利
- How did the audition go?     - Not so good.
慢着 你在学乔伊那招吗？
Wait a minute. Are you doing Joey's:
"试镜不太顺利 事实上很顺利对吧"
"The audition didn't go so well. Yeah, it did!"
没错
Yeah, I am!
- 班取得了第二次试镜的资格   - 太好了
- Yeah, Ben got a second audition.     - Oh, great.
对 我得教导罗斯我的戏分 因为我没有过关
Yeah, I had to teach Ross my bit because I actually didn't get a callback.
你也过关了 对吧？
You got a callback too, didn't you?
没错
Yeah, I did!
瑞秋 你怎么会来这里？
Hey, Rachel. What are you doing out here?
里头有点无聊 我想说来…
You know, it got kind of lonely up there, so I just thought I would come out here...
这里透透气
...and get some fresh air.
南西和我正好讨论到秋装
We were talking about the fall collection.
- 太好了   - 所以这是要…
- Oh, great.     - So anyway, we really...
- 抱歉 瞧你被我们熏的   - 没关系
- I'm sorry. We're smoking all over you.     - That's okay.
不成…你待着 我们走
No, no, no. We'll move. You stay there.
总之我把设计寄给罗夫 他很喜欢
I sent the designs to Ralph. He was excited about it.
太好了 你是最棒的
That's great. You are the best.
不好意思 能借支烟吗？
Excuse me. Can I bum one of those?
这个就好…
Actually, this one's...
你们在聊什么好笑的？
Okay, okay, okay. What's so funny over here?
我还以为你不抽烟的
I thought you didn't smoke.
我以为你们是说大麻烟
You know, I thought you guys meant marijuana cigarettes.
像是天使尘那种
You know what I mean? Like, doobies?
我还纳闷你们是疯了不成
Actually, I thought to myself, "Those guys are crazy."
没啦 我自己也抽烟 照三餐天天都抽
But no, actually, I smoke the regular ones all the time.
我们会抽大麻
We get high.
我也是
Me too.
- 闹你的   - 哦
- I'm kidding.     - Oh!
我也是
Me too.
老天 这真是折磨人 你是怎么习惯的？
Oh, God. This is so nerve-racking. How do you do this?
我过关的经验不多 所以…
Well, fortunately, I don't get many callbacks so...
我们在试镜之后被留下来 这是好现象吗？
Is it a good sign that they asked us to hang around after?
天知道
Who knows?
最后入围的是雷蒙 班 凯尔和乔伊
Okay. We have narrowed it down to Raymond, Ben, Kyle and Joey.
其余的人辛苦了 谢谢
The rest of you, thank you very much.
好耶 我就知道
Yes! I knew it!
再见
Ah. Bye-bye.
再会
So long.
后会有期
Later.
太棒了 我有可能饰演班的爸爸
This is great. I might actually get to play Ben's dad.
其实那是不可能的
Actually, that can't happen.
因为你们各自的长相都不同
Because you all have such different looks...
所以我们把你和雷蒙配对 凯尔和班是一组
...we're putting you with Raymond and Kyle with Ben.
所以最后只有一组会出线
So it'll either be you two or you two.
要命
Oh, man.
- 这样就有点尴尬了   - 真的是
- This is gonna be kind of weird.     - Yeah, it is.
对 一定会很尴尬
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
因为我们是最好的朋友 所以才会尴尬
No. We're like best friends. That's why it's weird.
哦 哦
Oh, oh.
原来如此… 我只是搭腔而已
I thought we were just talking.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我能把这些东西放这里 等着给瑞秋过生日吗？
Is it okay if I leave this stuff here till Rachel's birthday party?
- 当然可以 里头是什么？ - 杯子
- Uh, sure. What's in them?     - Um, cups.
那好 因为我们替瑞秋 准备了八百加仑的水
Oh, good, because we got Rachel 800 gallons of water.
老实说 这些杯子还真不少
Seriously, that's a lot of cups.
对 这是因为我负责杯子和冰块
Yeah, well, I'm in charge of cups and ice.
摩妮卡在这一天将后悔莫及 因为她要我负责杯子和冰块
And Monica's gonna rue the day that she put me in charge of cups and ice.
我也后悔过一次 除了后悔没做别的
You know, I rued the day once. Didn't get a whole lot else done.
好吧 该把其他杯子搬上来了
Okay, time to bring up the rest of the cups.
- 嘿 乔伊   - 嘿 菲比
- Hey, Joey.     - Hey, Pheebs.
- 嘿   - 罗斯 你在这里正好
- Hey.     - Ross, good, I'm glad you're here.
- 我有事要跟你说   - 怎么了？
- I want to talk to you about something.     - Oh. What's up?
我一直在想这次拍广告的事
Well, I've been thinking about this whole commercial thing.
我和班硬碰硬
You know me against Ben.
捉对厮杀 这样横竖都不会有好结果
The two of us competing. Well, that can't lead to anything good.
我想我还是退出好了
I think I'm just gonna step aside.
告诉他们我不去试镜
I'm gonna tell them that I won't audition.
哇哦
Wow. Uh...
乔伊 太好了 多谢
Joey, that's great. Thanks, man.
就这样？
That's it?
你真的要让我这样做？这事关我的职业生涯耶
You're gonna let me do this? This is my career we're talking about here.
可是你说…
But you just...
我是要你说出让班退出
I just said that so you wouldn't let Ben do it.
罗斯 如果真有人要退出 那也应该是班
Look, Ross, if anyone should step aside, it should be Ben.
- 什么？ - 钱德 告诉他为什么
- What?     - Chandler, tell him.
我先去开门
Well, let me get the door first.
没有人 你好
Oh, hi, no one.
为什么班应该退出？
Why should Ben step aside?
这原本就是他的试镜 你是跟过去的
It was his audition in the first place. You just tagged along.
就像是跟班老爹
You're like the tag-along dad.
起码我有顾虑到班的感受
At least I care about his feelings.
什么？
What?
你知道万一他没通过试镜 到时他会有多难过吗？
Do you know how hard this is gonna be on him when he doesn't get it?
那他又为什么不会通过？
And why wouldn't he get it?
得了吧 ？
Oh, come on.
你有没有看过跟我同组的小子有多厉害？
Have you seen what my kid can do? Huh?
他会拨电话 吃墨西哥脆片
I mean, he dials phones, he eats tortilla chips.
还会凭空踢足球演对手戏呢
He plays soccer with the cartoon tiger.
你是说你的小子喝汤 比我儿子厉害？
Are you saying your kid eats soup better than my kid?
你只是给他一根汤匙罢了
You just give him a spoon, baby.
- 是吗？我们走着瞧   - 好啊
- Oh, yeah? I guess we'll see.     - Yeah.
这支广告片的主角 非我和米契莫属
Because this commercial belongs to me and Mitch.
- 你的孩子叫做雷蒙   - 对？你的也是
- Your kid's name is Raymond.     - Yeah? So is yours.
(中央咖啡厅)
- 有没有用？ - 很棒…
- How did work go?     - Oh, it was great. It was great.
我听你们的建议去她们抽烟的地方 我们讨论到了生意
I went down there just like you said. And we talked business.
阿金完全接受我的意见
And Kim totally took my opinions.
你浑身烟味
You stink.
- 多谢   - 我是说真的
- Thanks.     - No, I'm serious.
因为那里的人全都在抽烟
That's because I went down there and they were smoking.
这其实是成功的味道
This is actually the smell of success.
不过有点怪怪的
But there's something different, though.
天啊 你有抽烟
Oh, my God. You smoked.
- 我没有   - 才怪
- I did not.     - Yes, you did.
你看起来生病又快乐 你一定有抽烟
You look happy and sick. You smoked.
好啦…我有抽 为了事业不得已嘛
All right, fine. But I had to. I had to do it for my career.
真希望我也可以 为了事业这么做
I wish I had to smoke for my career.
这样很恶心耶
That's so gross.
没那么糟啦
Well, no, it's not that bad, you know?
虽然舌头有点打结 手指也有点怪味
I mean, yeah, my tongue feels a little fuzzy and my fingers sort of smell.
其实我感觉快吐了
I actually feel like I could throw up.
好 但你一定要撑过这一关 再来就会是乐无比了
But you gotta push past this, okay? Because it's about to get so good.
钱德
Chandler.
你浑身烟味 我得去透透气
You smell so smoky, I gotta get up.
我没骗你
I'm not kidding.
我觉得你闻起来很香
I think you smell great.
所以大家都同意了 不要格子图案 要粉红？
So we're decided. No on plaid, yes on pink.
完全正确
Absolutely.
我举双手双脚赞成
I'm so onboard.
- 瑞秋 这支烟不是才刚点吗？ - 是啊
- Rachel, didn't you just light that?     - Yeah.
但是你知道什么？
But you know what?
我正在努力少抽烟
I'm just really, really trying to cut back, you know.
瑞秋 我等着看笑话
Good luck, Rach.
其实我最近有想要戒烟
I've actually been thinking about quitting.
我每周日晚上 都告诉自己要戒烟
Oh, well, sure. Every Sunday night, I tell myself I'm quitting.
结果周一还不是狂抽猛抽
Every Monday morning, it's like:
还用你说
Tell me about it.
那就戒了吧 我们一起戒烟
Well, let's quit. We'll just quit. Let's all quit.
听起来是很诱人啦
It does sound appealing.
- 我戒烟从没成功过   - 你可以的 一定行
- I never could do it.     - But you could. You can. Absolutely.
我们可以互相帮忙 用那个什么戒烟贴布的
We can help each other out. We could get those patches.
我们能组成戒烟三姐妹
We could be like the Patch Sisters.
其实我们真的应该戒烟 好吧 一起来戒烟
You know, we really should quit. Okay, let's quit.
好 太棒了 把香烟给我 来
Yes. Great. Give me those cigs. Come on.
通通交出来
Give it. Give it. Out. Done. Quit. Whoo!
- 那个打火机是我先生送我的   - 哈哈
- My late husband gave me that lighter.     - Ha, ha.
我没在开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
那好吧
Okay, then. Okay.
汤
Mm, soup.
乔伊 罗斯随时会到
Joey, Ross is gonna be here any second.
我去上个厕所 帮我看一下班 好吗？
Would you mind watching Ben while I use the ladies' room?
- 好啊 没问题   - 谢谢
- Yeah, no problem.     - Thanks.
嗯
Mm.
嗨 班
Hi, Ben.
你想当演员啊？告诉你 演戏可不像野餐
So you want to be an actor, huh? Well, I gotta tell you, it's no picnic.
有碰不完的钉子 一点都不稳定
There's tons of rejection. No stability.
前一天你还是德瑞克医生
I mean, one day, you're Dr. Drake Ramoray.
隔天你就要去啃蕃茄酱
The next day, you're eating ketchup right out of the bottle.
乔伊
Joey.
罗斯
Ross.
班
Ben.
班…
I mean, Ben. Ben.
雷蒙 乔伊 该你们上场了
Okay, Raymond, Joey, you're up.
- 嗨   - 好
- Hi.     - Okay.
好吧 我们来试一次 你们准备好了就开始
All right, well, let's try one. Whenever you guys are ready.
- 额   - 有问题吗？
- Uh-oh.     - Is there a problem?
这是面汤 我练习时是用蕃茄汤
Well, this is noodle soup. And I've been working with tomato.
不过没关系…
But that's okay. No problem. No problem.
面汤…
Mm, noodle soup.
你那样不错 不过台词是"汤"
You know, that's fine. But the line is, "Mm, soup."
- 那我刚才说什么？ - 面汤
- Oh. What'd I say?      - Mm, noodle soup.
有什么不一样？
How's that different?
对…
Oh. Right. Yeah.
好 我们来试一次
All right. Let's try one.
面汤
Mm, noodle soup.
好 我们再来次
Okay. Let's do it again.
好吧
Okay.
汤
Mm, soup.
我是说 不对 是 "面汤" "汤"
I mean, noodle soup. I mean, soup.
你争气点
Come on!
我们得换下一组了
You know what? We need to move on.
不… 我再演一次
Oh, no, I could do it one more time.
你看
See, look.
面汤…
Mm, noodle soup.
可恶
Damn it.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
被逮到了
Uh-oh. Busted.
你们这是在干嘛？
Come on, you guys. What are you doing?
我们不是戒烟姐妹花
I thought we were the Patch Sisters.
对 那样行不通
Yeah, that didn't work out.
瑞秋 我们有试着戒烟 但那实在是太难了
Rachel, we tried to quit. But it was too hard.
你们开始抽烟 起码也该告诉我嘛
Well, if you started smoking again, you could have at least told me.
快点来支 刚才说到哪里？不行
Come on, give me one of those. What are we talking about?
你戒烟很成功 不许放弃
No, you're doing great. Don't give up.
所以我们才没跟你说 我们不想拖你下水
That's why we didn't tell you, and we are not gonna drag you down.
等等 别这样 拖我下水…
Oh, wait. No, no. Drag me down. Drag me down.
瑞秋 万万不可 你戒烟成功 我们都替你骄傲
Forget it, Rachel. We're both so proud of how well you're doing.
我不能让你前功尽弃 若被我查到你有带烟 我一定炒你鱿鱼
I'm not gonna let you blow it. In fact, if I catch you, you're fired.
走吧 离开这里 我不要你吸二手烟
So go on, get out of here. Go on. I don't want you breathing this stuff. Go on.
那好 你和我一起去法国出差
So okay. So you'll come with me on the Paris trip?
要命
Oh, man.
你瞧瞧 杯子帽 杯子布条
Hey, check it out. Cup hat, cup banner...
杯子吊灯 还有本尊 杯子
...cup chandelier and the thing that started it all. The cup.
- 菲比 你对杯子还真有一套   - 哈哈
- Great job with the cups, Pheebs.     - Ha, ha.
你干脆跟她去约会算了
Why don't you just go out with her?
你有没有注意到冰？
Did you notice the ice? Look.
各式各样的都有 有碎冰 冰块还有干冰 注意看
We have it all. We have crushed, cubed and dry. Watch.
啊
Ah.
很有神秘感吧？
Mystical.
没人想吃我的小点心 他们全跑去吃菲比的雪花冰
No one's eating my Tuscan finger food. They're filling up on Phoebe's snow cones.
有雪花冰？
There are snow cones?
雪花冰最恶心了
Snow cones. Yuck.
- 你去吃啦   - 谢谢…
- Go, go.     - Thank you. Thank you.
- 注意…   - 惊喜
- Look, look.     - Surprise.
什么啊？一个月后才是我生日啊
What? My birthday is not for another month.
这样才惊喜啊
That's the surprise.
天啊 你们太棒了 我完全没想到
Oh, my God, you guys. This is so great. It's so unexpected.
钱德的生日还比我早到呢
I mean, Chandler's birthday's even before mine.
惊喜
Surprise.
真是太棒了 看看这些杯子
Wow. This is so great. Look at all these...
真的是怪怪的
...cups. This is so weird.
杯子是我负责的
I was in charge of cups.
好 那就没那么怪了
Oh, okay. Not so weird.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
我很遗憾你试镜不顺利
Listen, man. I'm sorry the audition didn't go well.
是喔
Yeah, right.
乔伊 我是真的很遗憾
No, really. I am, Joey. I feel bad.
罗斯 你用不着遗憾
Well, look, Ross. You don't have to, okay?
是我自己逊 怨不得你
It's not your fault I suck.
连"面汤"都说不好 还算哪门子的演员？
What kind of an actor can't even say, "Mm, noodle soup"?
你知道吗？或许你搞砸了试镜 不是因为你逊
Hey, you know what? Maybe you didn't mess up your audition because you suck.
或许你搞砸了试镜 是因为你更在意你的教子
Maybe you messed up because you care more about your godson.
- 什么意思？ - 我认为 在潜意识里…
- What do you mean?     - I think, subconsciously...
等等 我听不懂
Whoa, you lost me.
我觉得在某种程度上 你破坏了…
I think, on some level, you sabotaged...
自己的试镜好让班拿到那个角色
...your own audition so Ben would get the part.
你的说法比我的好多了
Well, your way sounds a lot better than mine.
对
Yeah.
- 对 不是我演技烂   - 不是
- Yeah. It's not that I'm a bad actor.     - No.
只是我念兹在兹都是班
No, it's just that, uh, I care so damn much about little Ben...
看到他成功对我来说更重要
...that, uh, it was more important for me to see him succeed.
- 就是这样 谢谢你   - 谢谢你
- There you go. Thank you.     - Thank you.
- 那他拿到角色没？ - 没有
- So did he get it?     - No.
不如意事十之八九嘛
Ah, what are you gonna do?
不好意思 瑞秋葛林在吗？我跟她约了吃中饭
Oh, hi. Excuse me. Is Rachel Green here? I'm supposed to meet her for lunch.
她现在不会下来这里了 她在十楼
Oh, she doesn't come down anymore. You can find her up on 10.
好…
Okay, great.
我们昨天中饭聊到提案报告
So we talked about the presentation at lunch.
他担心一个人出差不够看
He wondered if one person would be enough for me to take on the trip.
我说绝对没问题
And I said, "Yeah, absolutely."
后会有期了
I'll catch you guys later.